Alex Laties

387 Franklin Avenue, Apt 103 Brooklyn, NY 11238 Phone: 267 825 2530

Website: http://alex.laties.info/ E-Mail: alex@laties.info

General Purpose Software Developer

Alex Laties $^{^{\mathrm{TM}}}$ is a general purpose programmer that has worked on building, maintaining, and scaling web applications. He primarily works in Python, but has no strong language preference and has demonstrated some faculty with C, C#, Java, Ruby, PHP, and Javascript. He has worked in larger IDEs, such as Visual Studio, MonoDevelop, and XCode, but claims no great proficiencies in any of them. He primarily uses some hodge podge of Vim and assorted plugins as an IDE.

Alex has worked with teams in an agile style to quickly deliver features and products. He has worked with ticketing systems, such as Jira and Trello, to manage work loads. He has worked with source control systems, like Subversion and Git, to prevent himself and teammates from going crazy. He has worked in a test driven style and found it rather nice.

Alex has contributed some code to open source projects Bottle and pyrollbar.

Work History			
March 2012 - October 2013	Voxy, Inc	Software Engineer	• Worked with Django 1.3 on Python 2.7 to maintain a web application and mobile API.
			• Built prototypes for internal CRMs.
			• Built a new mobile API stack in Bottle.
			• Set up loadbalancing for web and mobile stacks using haproxy and pacemaker.
			• Set up and wrote initial recipes for Chef provisioning service.
			• Also dealt with PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Varnish, Celery, Redis, uwsgi, gunicorn, and nginx.
E 11/W: 4 0010	IID.		Assisted in the generation, collection, and processing
Fall/Winter 2010 - January 2011	UPenn School of Medicine	Lab Assistant	of data from experiments. Dealt with Matlab, Excel, and Python, as well as a variety of lab equipment.
Education			
Fall 2007 - Spring 2010	UPenn School of Engineering		Majored in Computer Science. Learned some theory, implemented a CPU, an OS shell, and some sweet buffer overflows. Also a little Chinese. Dropped out due to health reasons.